It's truly pitiful.
真是可悲
"They" even
“他们”居然
take in a child like you.
连你这种小孩子都要吸纳进来吗
What are you talking about?
你到底在说什么
What do you mean by a product of "Sabaramond"?
“塞巴拉隆多的产物”是什么意思
Is Mr. Sabaramond here too?
塞巴拉隆多先生也在这边的世界吗
Are you the people from the Empire over that world too?
你们也是从那边的世界 过来的帝国人吗
Or, are you related to the Kingdom of Nyanild?
还是说你们跟 努安伊路德王国有关系
I have never heard of this term before.
我没听过这个词语
Are you playing dumb with me?
你是在装傻吗
WATCH OUT FOR FIRES No, that's not right.It shouldn't be like that.
(小心火烛) 不 不对 应该不是那样
Are you not in cahoots with those people?
你和那群人不是一伙的吗
No, it's the same. It's enemy.
不对 他们是一样的 敌对
Who are you, Polka Shinoyama?
四乃山波尔卡 你是什么人
Damn it, there's no way to communicate with him.
可恶 根本没办法交流
The text on the walls was just welded on.
墙壁上的文字是刚刚才烧上去的
Could it be that he's nearby, observing the situation here?
他该不会就在附近 观察着这里的情况吧
There's no one else on this floor.
这一个楼层里没有其他人在
On the floor below, there is only Sayo.
楼下那一层只有小夜
There are a few people around the building.
大楼周围有几个人
There are two people on the rooftop?
屋顶上有两个人…
Uh, huh?
呃 咦
You're quite impressive, young man!
你挺厉害的嘛 少年
(Dead Mount, Death Play)
《尸体如山的死亡游戏》
(Episode 12: The Scared Place)
(#12 The Sacred Place -神殿-)
You truly surprised me.
你真是让我吃了一惊
You possess the talent to become a magician.
你拥有成为魔术师的才能
POUNDING IN THE HEART
(内心 怦砰 怦砰)
Who on earth is this kid?
见鬼了 这孩子到底是谁
Goddess of Luck, please grant me smooth communication with him.
幸运女神啊 请保佑我能和他顺利沟通吧
What's the deal with this guy?
这家伙是怎么回事
He's clearly slower than Heilei,
明明比“黑雷”的人还要慢
but I can't figure out his moves. He's really tough to deal with.
可我却看不清他的动作 真难对付
What exactly is his purpose for coming to see Polka?
他究竟是出于何种目的来见波尔卡的
Or perhaps he's here to find the fake Polka?
还是说他是来找假波尔卡的
Let me trick him into telling me some information.
让我来套一下他的话吧
So, old man, what are you here for?
所以 大叔你是来做什么的
Are you looking for Hosorogi?
难道你是来找细吕木的吗
Although I don't know who it is, let me make use of it.
虽然我不知道他说的是谁 但就让我利用一下吧
Hozologi, thank you.
夕律目 谢谢你咯
Wow, you actually saw through everything.
哎呀 居然被你看穿了
Fine.
罢了
I owe Hozologi a favor. I'll find another opportunity to repay the favor.
夕律目对我有恩 我还是另找机会还他人情好了
That's settled then!
就这么定了
Good luck and good night. Goddess of Luck!
Good luck&Good night 幸运女神
You owe Hosorogi a favor?
细吕木对你有恩…
Why would the prosecutor help a wanted criminal like you?
警察的检察官 为什么会帮助你这样的通缉犯
Is it possible that the police sniping was self-directed?
你受到警方的狙击这件事 该不会是你自导自演的吧
I didn't expect that I would make the wrong choice!
没想到我居然做出了错误的选择
PHEW Wake up, Goddess of Luck!
(呼呼) 快醒过来啊 幸运女神
His heart rate increased.
他的心跳变快了
Because what I said was right?
被我说中了吗
Such a pity.
真可惜
ROUGH SELF-INVENTED WORDS That sniper attack was undeniably "other-directed".
(粗糙的自创词) 那起狙击是货真价实的“他导他演”
LANGUAGE STRUCTURE CONFUSION However, since I was targeted for a sniper attack,
(混乱的语言组织) 不过既然我受到了狙击
it indicates that something has happened to Hozologi.
那就说明夕律目的身上发生了什么
This worries me greatly,
(混乱的语言组织) 这实在是让我很担心
LANGUAGE STRUCTURE CONFUSION so I came here to see if I could find any clues.
所以我才会来这看看 能不能找到一些线索
I see.
原来如此
POLKA, HOSOROGI, OLD MAN So what exactly is his relationship with Hosorogi?
(波尔卡 细吕木 大叔) 他跟细吕木到底是什么关系
Forget it.
算了
Regardless of whether he is the enemy of Master,
无论他是不是主公大人的敌人
I will find ways to capture him and make him confess honestly.
我都得想尽办法抓住他 让他老实交代一切
Oh my, oh my, it seems like you're not ready to give up.
哎呀哎呀 看来你是不想要停手了
I advise you to dismiss this idea. This time, it's your turn to be startled.
我劝你还是打消这个念头吧 不然就变成你要受到惊吓了
That's really something to look forward to.
那还真是让人期待
I wonder what you will use to startle me!
你到底会用什么方法让我感到惊吓呢
Lemmings!
旅鼠军团…
Like an urban legend, the Jack-of-All-Trades stops at nothing.
如都市传说一般无所不为的万事屋
A monster. The true identity remains unknown.
怪物 真身不明
My clan, the Heilei,
吾之一族“黑雷”
was under strict orders not to lay a hand on him.
严令“绝不能对其出手”的一个人
Could it be that he is your comrade, old man?
这家伙该不会也是大叔你的同伴吧
I was right, wasn't I? You were indeed startled.
我说得没错 你果然吓了一跳吧
I was startled too.
我也被吓了一跳
He is a dangerous man.
他是个危险的男人
Even I can't understand what he intends to do.
就连我也不清楚他打算做什么
I truly don't understand.
我是真的啥都不知道啊
If you want to surrender and run away, do it now.
若是你想投降和逃跑 就趁现在吧
ESCAPE ROUTE, ABOVE I want to run away too.
(逃跑路线 上方) 我也好想逃跑啊
I know who you are.
我知道这家伙是谁
I do not know your real name, but you are called "Lemmings."
虽然不清楚他的本名叫什么 但他被赋予了旅鼠军团这一绰号
You possess extraordinary skills, and your profession is unknown.
身怀绝技 职业不详
The enigmatic baby-face boy,
充满谜团的童颜少年啊
don't provoke the fierce warrior over there.
你不要激怒那边的狂战士
NOT A SINGLE LIE Once he makes a move,
(没有半点谎言) 他一旦出手
even I can't stop him.
就连我也没法阻止
Ah, am I going to die?
唉 我是不是完蛋了
He's full of flaws.
浑身都是破绽
Do the guards of Lord Rozan know about Lemmings?
吕算大人的护卫们 知道旅鼠军团的事吗
I haven't told my family the details about you guys.
我没跟家人说过你们的详细情况
Perhaps someone saw Lemmings during the previous fire incident.
但 也许有人在之前的那起火灾当中 看到了旅鼠军团
If so…
既然如此…
Don't worry.
你放心
I won't do anything that would hurt our own people.
我不会做伤害自己人的事
I have carefully instructed Lemmings
我仔细叮嘱过旅鼠军团
not to harm my Grandpa's guards.
让他不要对老爷子的护卫出手
As long as it is my command, he will definitely obey.
只要是我下的命令 他就一定会遵守
No matter what happens.
不管发生什么事
What's going on?
什么情况
What's the matter with this guy?
这家伙到底是怎么回事啊
Ignoring me?
竟敢无视我…
It is uncuttable.
我切不断…
Then, how about this?
那么 这招如何
Normally, shouldn't you charge towards the enemy using electric shocks to you
通 通常来说 你不应该 抱着同归于尽的信念
with the determination to die together?
扑向对你使出电击的敌人吗
I really want to sound the alarm for young people like you in this modern society
我真想对你这种连自身触电 都毫不在乎的现代社会的年轻人
who don't even care about getting electrocuted.
敲响警钟
So he's not your comrade at all.
原来他根本不是你的同伴啊
That's hard to say.
这可不好说
For me, everything in my surrounding environment is considered a comrade.
对我而言 环绕在自身周围的 环境内的一切事物都是同伴
That means both the person wrapped in bandages
也就是说包括那个缠绷带的人 以及少年你在内
and you can be called my comrades.
都称得上我的同伴
I'M COUNTING ON YOU Let's just stop killing each other.
(拜托你了) 自相残杀就到此为止吧
Why don't we communicate with each other to solve the problem?
不如让我们心平气和地来解决问题吧
You've been playing boring tricks since earlier.
你这家伙从刚才开始 就一直在弄些无聊的把戏
I've had enough. I'll just knock both of you out.
我受够了 我干脆把你们两个一起揍飞算了
Can I have a moment of your time, miss?
可以稍微占用你一点时间吗 小姐
We are not suspicious individuals.
我们不是什么可疑的人
We are Shinjuku Police's Community Safety Division officers.
是隶属于新宿警察局 生活安全科的警察
I'm curious why you're dressed like this
我有点好奇 明明没有下雨
when it's not raining at all.
为什么你却穿成了这样
A young child walks the streets at three in the morning.
半夜三点有孩子还在街上闲逛
As a police officer, I cannot turn a blind eye to it.
作为警官 我无法坐视不管啊
WATCH OUT FOR FIRES
(小心火烛)
CALL ENDED
(通话结束)
He hangs up.
他挂掉了…
What's going on? What happened?
什么情况 发生什么事了
Although it's just fragmented information,
虽说不过是零碎的内容
the intelligence from the world I once lived in has indeed spread over here.
但我曾经待过的那个世界的情报 确实传播到了这边
A product of Sabaramond?
“塞巴拉隆多”的产物吗
The world I escaped from
我逃离的世界
holds precious memories of
那是成为“世界的敌人”
irreplaceable people and me,
沾染污秽 无法回头的我
the world's enemy who cannot turn back.
和那群无可替代的人们的回忆之地
Stop! Don't touch it.
住手 不要碰
Don't tarnish it.
不要玷污它
Among those few people on the rooftop,
屋顶上那几个人
one is undoubtedly Lemmings.
其中一个毫无疑问是“旅鼠军团”
Meanwhile, the person downstairs seems extremely frantic.
而楼下那人的气息则显得非常慌乱
Just after hanging up the phone, this situation occurred.
电话刚挂断就出现了这样的情况
It indicates that the person I was talking to is very likely nearby.
说明跟我通话的对象 极有可能就在附近
I can't overlook any possible clue at the moment.
现在我不能放过任何一丝线索
The first thing to do is to
我首先要做的
control the current situation.
就是压制住当下的局面
What's wrong, Romelka?
罗梅卡 你怎么了
Easlies.
伊斯莉丝
Why have you been gazing at the sea?
你为何一直眺望着海面
I'm just immersed in sadness, that's all.
我只是沉浸在感伤当中罢了
I recall the pitiful yet elegant empire
我想起了远在一百多年前就毁灭的
THE FORMER SECOND-RANKED IMPERIAL COURT SORCERER TO THE BYANDY EMPIRE that perished over a hundred years ago.
(原巴亚蒂帝国宫廷魔术师第二席) 可怜又优雅的帝国
ROAMING WOODLANDS, SEVENTH-RANKED You're lying. Stop lying.
(同 第七席 散步树海) 少骗人了 你绝对是在说谎
ROMELKA RIMELKA You're thinking about Corpse God, aren't you?
(罗梅卡 莉梅卡) 你是在想“尸神殿”的事吧
It doesn't make a difference.
差不多吧
All I did in the empire was
我在帝国做的事
nurturing that foolish disciple.
无非就是培养了那个笨蛋徒弟
This achievement is truly remarkable!
这功绩已经相当了不得了啊
It is unusual for a master and a disciple to both be court wizards.
师徒一起位列宫廷魔法师之位 可是相当少见的情况呢
I only took over my master's position after he retired.
就连我都是在师傅退位后 才接替了他的位置
Corpse God, known for his unparalleled strength,
实力首屈一指的“尸神殿”
utilizes necromancy that is distinct from yours.
使用的是跟伊斯莉丝 方向性相异的死灵术
It's just like entrusting each other's backs to one another
这有一种师徒将各自的后背 托付给彼此的感觉
as master and disciple, which is truly exhilarating.
真是让人的心怦怦乱跳
I can even feel the magic wandering through veins. It's simply irresistible.
我甚至还能感到魔力在叶脉里游走 简直就让人欲罢不能
Even after a hundred years, you still remain unruly.
就算过去了一百年 你的舌头还是不老实呢
By utilizing magic to extend your lifespan,
借助魔法延长寿命后
your growth has also slowed down.
该不会连你的成长 也一并变得迟缓下来了吧
Perhaps that foolish disciple will
说不定那个笨蛋徒弟
Isn't that great? Forever being a child.
那不是挺好的吗 永远都是小孩子
Corpse God is usually a very good child.
“尸神殿”平日里是个很好的孩子
However, once he enters the battlefield, he changes.
可一旦踏上战场 他就像是变了个人似的
A good child. A good child?
好孩子 好孩子吗
No, you've got it wrong,
你搞错了
and you're completely mistaken.
而且是大错特错
That foolish disciple surpasses me in one aspect.
那个笨蛋徒弟有一处胜于我
He is capable of empathy.
那便是共情能力
Empathy?
共情…
Although he himself is not aware of this,
虽说他自己并未察觉到这一点
he lacks autonomy almost entirely.
但他几乎不具备自主性
He entrusts himself entirely to those he considers companions.
他会将自己的全部 托付给他认为是同伴的人
Perhaps it is precisely because of this
也许就是因为这样
that he surpasses me in the aspect of synchronizing with the deceased.
唯有跟死者“同步”的这一能力 他远胜于我
Therefore, precisely because of this,
所以 正因如此
even if he is treated unfairly, he doesn't care at all.
即便自身遭到不公的对待 他也毫不在意
However, once the "sanctuary" he relies on is defiled,
而一旦他依存的“归宿”遭到玷污
that fellow, the Corpse God,
那家伙“尸神殿”就会…
will completely lose control.
彻底失控
Although I don't know what happened,
虽然不知道发生了什么
I was advised to pay attention to the condition of the building.
但我被叮嘱过要注意大楼周围的状况
It's quite chilling to see a high school girl wearing a raincoat
明明没有下雨却穿着雨衣的女高中生
when it's not raining at all.
有点让人毛骨悚然啊
After all, we have the example of The Gator Sisters.
毕竟有“鳄鱼姐妹”这个例子在
Even if it is a girl, I should not take it lightly.
即便是女孩子也不能掉以轻心…
I'm very sorry.
十分抱歉
Actually, it's because our dog ran away from home,
其实是因为我家里养的狗跑了出来
so my father and I came here together to look for it.
所以我和我爸爸就一起来这里找它了
It seems like it ran into this building.
然后我们就发现 它好像跑进了这栋大楼里…
Where is your father?
那你父亲呢
He called just now and said he found our dog, Toyomaru.
他刚才打电话给我说他找到了丰丸 也就是我们家里养的狗
I think it won't be long before my father comes back.
我想我爸爸马上就会过来了
Here he is.
啊 来了来了
Dad.
爸爸
What do you want from my daughter?
你们找我女儿有事吗
Dad, don't make that expression.
爸爸 不要摆出那种表情啦
They are police officers.
他们是警察
Sorry for my rudeness.
真是抱歉
I am here with my daughter looking for our dog.
我在和女儿一起找家里养的狗
Why do you need to wear raincoat?
你为什么要穿雨衣
To avoid soiling the clothes worn when searching in tight spaces.
这是为了避免在狭窄的地方寻找时 弄脏我身上穿的衣服
No, there are no living dogs nearby.
不对 附近并没有活着的狗
I am somewhat familiar
和警官对话的那个女孩灵魂的颜色
with the color of the girl's soul who had a conversation with the police officer
以及在屋顶上和“旅鼠军团”对峙的 那个男人的灵魂的颜色
and the color of the man's soul who confronted Lemmings on the rooftop.
两者我都有些熟悉
Both of them asked about
在占卜的时候
the "emblem" during divination.
他们都问了关于“国徽”的事
This is not a coincidence.
这不是偶然
I'll expand the temple more.
我将神殿略微扩展一些吧
What's wrong?
怎么了
Hey, don't you feel cold?
喂 你不觉得很冷吗
Young man, let's review the basics today.
少年 我们今天就来复习一下基础吧
Let's start with The Netherworld,
首先是“异界溢流”
also known as the construction of the temple.
先从构筑神殿开始吧
Have you ever felt the forest covered in silence at night to be eerie?
你是否曾觉得夜晚 笼罩在寂静当中的森林很可怕
As if in a temple, the atmosphere is sacred.
仅仅是站在那里便能够感受到 犹如置身神殿当中的那种神圣的氛围
Necromancers only need to overflow
施术者只要在自己的周围
netherworld air into an enclosed space
或是某个封闭的空间 混入“彼岸”的空气
or the necromancer's surroundings
就能在某种程度上
to freely create an "atmosphere" that may be unseen but can be felt to some extent.
恣意地创造出虽看不到 却能够感受到的“氛围”
The sensation described is incredibly subtle for individuals without Evil Eye.
这种感受对于不具备 “亚眼”的人来说极其微小
If you devote enough time to the ritual,
但只要花费启动仪式的时间
the ritual can be used to confuse others' vision and orientation.
便可达到扰乱方向感 和视觉的幻术效果
Your current level is approximately at this stage.
你现在的水平大概就是这样了
Don't be impatient, young man.
不要心急 少年
If you continue to cultivate and train,
若是你继续修练下去
there will come a day when you can encompass an entire city.
终有一日你也能覆盖一城之地
Did you feel it suddenly gets so cold?
你有没有觉得突然变冷了
Oh my, even though I'm not sure what's going on,
哎呀哎呀 虽然不清楚怎么回事
this atmosphere makes me feel a bit uneasy.
但是这氛围让人感到有点不舒服呢
The "Lemmings" is on the rooftop,
“旅鼠军团”在屋顶上
and I don't want to confront him directly.
我不想和他正面交锋
But both the rooftop and the entrance below
可是屋顶和下面的入口
have had people asking about the emblem.
都有来询问过“国徽”的人
If they have some kind of clue in their hands,
如果他们手里握有某种线索
I absolutely cannot let them escape.
我就绝不能让他们逃走
First, I need to support Xiaoyu.
首先我要去支援小幽
WE WILL BE SEEN BY THE PEOPLE AROUND
(会被周围的人看到的)
Don't worry.
没事的
What I'm about to do now is to unleash the "Swarm of Invisible Hands."
我现在要使出的是“无形之手”
What's going on here?
这是怎么回事
The atmosphere around suddenly changed.
周围的气氛突然产生了变化
It feels like sinking to the bottom of a lake.
感觉像是沉到了湖底一样
Although the scenery remains unchanged,
景色虽然没有任何变化
there is definitely something different.
但的确有什么变得不一样了
Could it be that someone released some kind of gas?
难道是有人释放了某种气体吗
No, that's not it.
不对
This thing has no effect on the body.
这东西对身体并无影响
It simply makes people feel uncomfortable.
只是单纯地让人感到不舒服
I should probably leave this place right now.
看来此地不宜久留
Ah… by the way,
啊 那个
let me ask first,
姑且让我先问一下
which one of you did this?
这是你们当中的哪一位干的呢
How could I possibly know?
我怎么可能知道
What just happened? What's going on?
刚 刚才那是什么 发生什么事了
Even in such an extraordinary situation, you are still targeting me?
即使身处如此异常的情况当中 你还是咬着我不放吗
What?
什么
What's going on? There has been something since then that's hindering us.
怎么回事 从方才开始就有某种东西 在妨碍我们
From what I observed, that young man didn't make any moves.
据我观察 那个少年倒是没什么动作
In other words, that thing has a clear purpose and is specifically targeting us.
也就是说那东西是带有明确的目的 来专门针对我们的吗
The condition is very good.
状况十分良好
Sharing sensations or sympathizing with the dead is easy.
不论是跟死灵共鸣还是共享触觉 实现起来都相当容易
Even within the Temple that is currently unfolding,
即便我要在如今展开的“神殿” “异界溢流”的结界里
it is not difficult to operate precisely within The Netherworld's borders.
进行精密的操作也不成问题
So, let's move on to the next stage.
那么 就进入下一阶段吧
Although I'm very interested, let's end the playtime with you tonight.
虽然我对这情况很感兴趣 但我今晚就陪你们玩到这里吧
Até breve obri… What's the next sentence again?
Até breve obri… 后面是啥来着
Oh dear, it seems like one thing after another.
哎呀哎呀 真是一波未平一波又起
As expected, if it's just me, I can't effectively advertise.
果然只有我一个人的话 根本起不到打广告的效果啊
Recruiting!
急征
HERE I need extras to play the role of ropes.
(这里) 我需要饰演绳子的群众演员
Ah, it looks like I should report this matter to Mr. Iwa.
啊 看来我得向岩先生 报告一下这件事了
That shouldn't be a problem.
这倒是没问题
But where are you going to start?
可你打算从何说起啊
What?
什么
That is also a trick of Solitaire, right?
“那个”也是雪天鸦的戏法吧
Hahaha, it's hard to say.
哈哈哈 这可不好说
My secret blend of smoke
我的秘制烟雾
combines tapioca powder to recreate the taste of pearl milk tea.
为了重现珍珠奶茶的味道 可是混合了木薯粉…
This is…
这是…
This is the necromancy I have created by adapting to the world here.
这是我根据这边的世界进行调整 从而创造出的死灵术
Yes?
是我
I'm sending the video over now. Please watch it immediately.
我现在将视频发送过去 请您立刻进行确认
What happened?
发生什么事了
Given the current situation, I find it difficult to make a judgment.
眼下的事态我难以做出判断
What did you say?
这是什么…
Establishing perceptual sharing through Sympathizing with the Dead and Spirit-of-the-Dead Thread.
通过“死灵共鸣” 与“死灵之手”建立感知共享
This was not successfully achieved in my previous world
这在我之前的那个世界里
due to obstacles from abundant magical elements.
因为受到丰富的魔素的阻碍 而没法顺利实现
You're here too, the Firestarter?
原来你也来了啊 “赴火之虫”
You misdirected me, quite skilled indeed.
居然对我进行了误导 很有一手嘛
Fine. You ask me why I don't mind?
算了 你问我为什么不计较
That's because I'm in a great mood right now.
那自然是因为我现在心情很棒
Although it hasn't been confirmed yet,
虽说我目前还没有确定
the bridge forged by immense hope is now shining brightly before me like a rainbow.
但是由巨大希望建成的桥梁 如今就在我面前如彩虹般熠熠生辉
Due to the lack of magical elements in this world, this move is easy to perform.
在这个魔素稀少的世界 我可以完美地使出这一招
And in order to enable interference at physical level,
而且 为了能够进行物理层面的干涉
I will weave the Threads in the hands of the necromancer.
我在死灵之手上编入“灵线”
This extraordinary technique exploits the unique environment of this world.
这招绝技正是利用了 这个世界特有的环境
I shall name it the Swarm of Invisible Hands.
我将它命名为“无形手群”
Time passes, conventions are shattered.
时间流转 常识颠覆
This world is truly magnificent!
这世间是如此的美丽
The energy I output is still not enough to suppress Lemmings.
我输出的能量还不足以压制旅鼠军团
In that case, I will deal with the other person first.
既然如此 我就先将另一个人…
The imaged middle schooler inside me
我体内的幻想初中生
is cheering and jumping with joy.
正在欢呼雀跃着
Are the "bones" and "arms" at the scene
火灾现场的“骨头”以及“手臂”
of the fire of the same origin?
都来自于相同地方吗
And do you hold this secret?
而你则握有这一秘密吗
I see.
原来如此
Your title carries no hint of falsehood.
你的名号并无半点虚假
I will see you again.
再会吧
Corpse God, I will surely expose your true identity.
“尸神殿” 我必定会揭露你的真实身份
As for you, if possible, I really don't want to see you again,
至于你 如果可以的话 我实在是不想再见到你了
Lemmings.
旅鼠军团
DID HE ESCAPE?
(被他跑掉了吗?)
The person on the rooftop has escaped,
屋顶上的那个人是逃掉了
but I got the one downstairs.
不过 楼下的那个被我逮到了
THIS INCIDENT IS SO SHOCKING, WHAT EXACTLY HAPPENED?
(这次的事件太令人震惊了) (到底发生了什么事)
WHO DID IT?
(是谁干的?)
THERE WON'T BE ANY MISTAKES
(不会有错的)
ANOTHER PARANORMAL PHENOMENON APPEARED? IS IT RELATED TO THE PREVIOUS FIRE INCIDENT?
(又有灵异现像出现了!?) (这次和之前的大楼火灾有什么关联吗?)
BONES WERE MOVING IN THE FIRE?
(火灾里有骨头在动!?)
-That is a mysterious power passed down from ancient times. -Sacred arts, necromancy, elven arts.
-那是古代流传下来的一种神秘力量 -神圣术 死灵术 精灵术
Those are the secret arts of our ancestors, which we have yet to master.
那是我等祖辈都未能掌握的 遥远故乡的秘术
-Lost power. -A power that guides us towards a new stage.
-失落的力量 -是引导我等迈向崭新阶段的力量
-It must be governed. -It is both power and duty.
-必须进行管理 -是权力也是义务
-Explore, explore, search. -Explore, debate, discover, seize.
-探索 探索 搜寻 -探索 争论 发现 抢夺
We must obtain it.
必须得到它
I UNDERSTAND, MY FELLOW BRETHREN, WE WILL TRY TO USE THE PIECES IN OUR HANDS
(我明白了 同胞们 我们会尽量动用手里的棋子)
AS LONG AS THE PIECES ARE USED CORRECTLY, THE PROBLEM CAN BE SOLVED SIMULTANEOUSLY
(只要棋子用得对 问题就能同时解决)
HOW IRONIC IT IS
(还真是讽刺啊)
TO MY SURPRISE, INSIDE THE BUILDING WHERE HOSOROGI WAS ELIMINATED
(没想到除掉细吕木的那栋大楼里)
THERE WAS ACTUALLY A GATHERING OF INDIVIDUALS WHO INHERITED HIS WILL
(居然聚集了一群继承他的意志的人)
Is that so? I got it.
是吗 我明白了
Anyway, you take control of the scene, Yatsu.
总之你先控制住现场 八津
It seems like the police are taking action.
警察貌似有动作了
This city was originally bustling.
这座城市原本就很热闹
It looks like it's going to become noisy again.
看来又要变得嘈杂起来了呢
Things are getting interesting, Sister.
事情变得有趣起来了 姐姐
(Dead Mount, Death Play S2)
(《尸体如山的死亡游戏》第二季)
SEE YOU IN OCTOBER
(我们十月份见)